[In My Prime]
[Episode 3]
Aihua.
Why are you sleeping at this hour?
How many times have I emphasized
the rules at the mine?
No sleeping underground or at the pithead.
Look at you!
They are looking to
make an example of someone right now.
Aren't you just asking for trouble?
Dongfang,
I just dozed off for a bit.
Don't call me Dongfang.
It's working hours now.
Be serious!
Alright, alright.
Chief Cao.
Don't worry.
I just dozed off for a bit.
It won't hold things up.
Alright.
I'll go down the mine then.
Stop right there!
Come with me to my office
and write a formal apology.
Dongfang.
No,
Chief Cao.
I promise
I won't make mistakes again.
This is the last time.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
It's mainly because I've been going down the mine
for a few nights,
and I really couldn't take it anymore.
Going down the mine for a few nights?
Well...
You weren't even scheduled
for the recent night shifts.
I thought
if I could go down one more time,
I would.
Last time,
I took Sweetie to Haizhou
to see a doctor.
The doctor said
her "white hair" condition
needs long-term care.
Things like Vitamin C
and other common medicines
must always be kept at home.
So I thought
I'd save more money
to buy medicine for her.
Aihua.
Qi Shi's medical bills
are on me from now on.
That won't do.
I can't always let you pay.
You gave me money last time.
Dongfang.
No, Chief Cao.
If you just let me off this time,
you'll be doing me a huge favor.
Otherwise, three months' salary
will be gone.
I still have a family to feed.
Please?
Thank you, Dongfang.
No, thank you, Chief Cao.
Thank you, Chief Cao.
I promise
there won't be a next time.
There won't be a next time.
We're colleagues.
Just give me an employee discount.
Next time,
when you come to our place
to buy groceries,
I'll give you some extra.
I can't make that call.
Go talk to Hu Yitong.
Okay, okay.
I'll go find Hu Yitong.
Not bad, not bad.
Take this one.
Welcome.
Qi Shi,
you're starting school soon,
right?
Take a look at these things.
Whatever you like,
just tell me.
It's
a back-to-school gift for you,
okay?
Go take a look.
Cao Xin,
didn't you want that
"One Hundred Thousand Whys"?
I will buy it for you today,
okay?
Look.
These two colors are different.
Excuse me.
Please get me this,
"One Hundred Thousand Whys".
Sure.
This whole set, right?
Yes.
You get the toy car,
and I'll buy "One Hundred Thousand Whys".
I'll do your homework for a week
in exchange.
Half a month.
Deal.
I like cars.
Uncle Cao.
Qi Shi likes cars, huh?
Alright.
Okay.
Qi Shi wants the car,
and Cao Xin wants the books.
Right?
-Yes.
Okay.
Cao Xin.
Drink your milk.
Good job.
Are you tired?
Isn't this Qi Shi's?
Why do you have it?
Qi Shi said
Aunt Huo has been
in a bad mood these days,
so she left the toy car model
with me for now.
Your Aunt Huo
has a sharp tongue,
but deep down,
she's warmer than anyone.
At school,
take good care of Qi Shi.
Don't let anyone bully her.
Got it?
I want to wear a red scarf to school too.
You're not a Young Pioneer yet.
Why would you wear a red scarf?
Go to sleep now.
Cao Xin wears one,
so I want to wear one too.
Did you put the magnifying glass
in your backpack?
I did.
Go to sleep.
My daughter is so pretty.
Is this really my daughter?
Is this really my sister?
Sweetie,
do you know what this is called?
It's called
a mouse falling into a water jar.
What does that mean, Dad?
It means you look slick!
From now on,
no one will laugh at you anymore
and call you the White-Haired Girl.
Thanks, Dad.
We're family, no need to thank me.
This is all...
Sweetie,
Dad has another
secret weapon for you.
Look.
From now on,
if the words on the blackboard
are too small for you to see,
just use this.
Look.
Then
look through it like this.
Come on, try it.
How is it?
Thanks, Dad.
All right.
Go eat your breakfast.
Otherwise, on your first day,
you'll be late for school.
Hurry up.
Honey,
I should give you an award.
The Award for Selfless Dedication.
Look.
Our daughter looks so energetic today.
It's clearly all your doing.
But you
gave all the credit to me,
letting me take such a big advantage.
Honey.
What kind of blessing did I earn
in my past life
to marry a wonderful wife like you?
Do you think everyone is like you,
making a fuss over the smallest thing
and letting the whole world know?
Aihua.
Dongfang.
Today is Qi Shi's first day of school.
Let me take her.
No need.
I'll take her.
Let me take her.
Cao Xin is going too.
You just do your work.
No need to take up your time.
Let me take her.
Cao Xin.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Starting today,
Qi Shi
is a proud
elementary school student.
Come, get down.
Qi Shi.
If anything happens,
find the teacher. Do you hear me?
Or go find Cao Xin.
Cao Xin,
take good care of Qi Shi.
Don't let anyone bully her.
Do you hear me?
Okay, go.
Qi Shi,
don't be nervous.
Cao Xin, take good care of Qi Shi.
Don't let anyone bully her.
Isn't this Qi Zhi's
monster sister?
Yeah.
Isn't she the White-Haired Girl?
Yeah, how did your hair turn black?
What do you think?
You can't master this skill
without over ten years of practice.
It's so accurate.
My hand is a scale.
And look at this scale.
It's facing you,
I don't even need to look at it.
I even perform this
when foreign guests come.
Two bucks.
Okay.
Take care.
Qinglian.
Did you know?
Cao Dongfang's family
got a telephone installed.
I heard
it cost 4,000 yuan,
and they had to
find connections to wait in line
just to get it.
Spending so much money on that thing.
Why install it? Honestly.
I wouldn't install one
even if I had the money.
If I had money, I'd save it
for the kids' education.
Exactly.
Our mine is so small.
You can hear a fart
from one end to the other.
And he still installed a phone.
Yeah.
What a show-off.
Why...
Why does my left eye keep twitching?
Could Qi Shi
be getting into trouble
on her first day at school?
Let me see, let me see, let me see.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Four, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, stop.
Do you want to see a magic show?
Let's see. What magic?
Black to white, white to black.
You can't tell the difference.
Where is it?
Let's go!
Give it back to me!
Come and get it.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come and get it.
Why aren't you grabbing it?
Come and grab it.
Come and get it if you can.
Hold this.
How dare you hit me?
What are you two doing? Come help.
Can't find your glasses?
Can't see, right?
Teach her a lesson.
How dare you hit my sister?
You're asking for this!
Boss, are you okay?
Qi Zhi, you've got nerve.
Delivering yourself to us.
Let's beat him up too!
That's for bullying my sister!
I'll kill you!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Wear it, quick.
Kick him!
Let me go!
Kick him. Kick him!
Kick him!
Let go!
Get out of here.
It's none of your business!
Let go of me!
Get out of here!
Let me go!
You brat!
Are you a dog?
I...
The teacher is here!
Who's fighting? Stop!
Let go of your hands.
The spring breeze blows.
[Qingwu Elementary School]
Blowing the willows green.
Speak.
Who started it?
She started it.
I don't even know how I provoked her.
She acted like she was crazy.
My... my arm
was sprained by her.
I can't even move it now.
My face is ruined by her scratches.
My sister's face is ruined too.
You even broke her glasses.
Principal,
we demand she be expelled.
If anyone gets expelled,
it should be you first!
Three 6th graders
were beating up a second grader.
Shameless!
Who are you calling shameless?
Say that again!
Shameless!
A little conflict between students
is normal, isn't it?
I'll go tell my dad.
My dad is the mine director.
A mine director outrank
a principal, right?
Let my dad judge who's right.
You troublemakers.
You came here
quite often, don't you?
None of you are easy to deal with.
But no matter what,
hitting people is always wrong.
Tell you what.
The student who threw the first punch
should apologize,
and we'll let this matter go.
Hurry up and apologize!
Say something!
An apology is letting you off easy.
If you don't apologize,
you'll be expelled.
Qi Shi.
Apologize for what?
What did you do wrong?
Look at this.
Let everyone see.
Her injuries
are no less severe than theirs.
She's just a girl.
Who will take responsibility
if she's badly hurt?
My dad is rich. I'll take responsibility.
Just because your dad
is the mine director,
you think you can bully my daughter,
right?
Fine, fine, fine.
School is just letting out now.
Let's have the other parents judge
and see what kind of atmosphere
this school has.
No need to do that.
Principal.
I know my own daughter
very well.
She doesn't cause trouble,
but she's definitely not afraid of it.
Right, right.
I can figure it out
with my eyes closed.
These brats
bullied my daughter first.
Exactly!
Do you admit it or not?
Admit what?
Everyone saw it.
She started it.
Who saw it?
Tell me, who saw it?
Principal, he's lying.
Our whole class saw it.
Those three
bullied Qi Shi first.
Tian Zihao,
isn't that right?
Principal,
I can testify.
Our whole class saw it.
Tell me,
did you guys
bully Qi Shi first?
If you don't tell the truth,
I'll go find your mom later.
Zhou Xuanyu suddenly took off
Qi Shi's wig
and wouldn't give it back to Qi Shi.
That's why they started fighting.
Principal,
you heard that, right?
Zhou Xuanyu clearly started it,
yet he twisted the facts
and blamed my daughter.
Let me tell you,
you deserved to be beaten.
You're so pathetic. You asked for it.
You've completely disgraced
your father.
Principal,
my daughter wasn't fighting.
It was self-defense.
If she hadn't fought back,
she would be condoning school bullying.
It's encouraging bad behavior.
It's undermining
the standards of civility, morality,
and good conduct.
My mom is absolutely right.
Hey, you.
The principal just said
whoever started it should apologize.
Say sorry to Qi Shi.
Say it!
Sorry.
Principal.
The matter is settled.
I won't bother you anymore.
I have to go home
and cook for my children.
You guys be careful from now on.
Let's go.
No wonder Qi Shi is so amazing.
Like mother, like daughter.
If only I had a mom like that.
How awesome would that be?
If only I had
a mom like that.
I could walk around
like I own the school.
Right, Sis?
Cao Xin.
Cao Xin, Si.
Dad.
I heard you got into a fight.
Where is Qi Shi?
Come on, take me to your teacher.
This is outrageous!
Dad, we're all fine.
Aunt Huo just came
and took Qi Shi home.
Glad you're fine.
If this happens again,
tell me.
I'll stand up for you.
Don't let others bully you.
Dad, I listened to you today.
As soon as something went wrong,
I hurried to get the teacher.
Cao Xin is such a good boy.
Here, have some candy.
Dad,
I was awesome today too.
During the fight,
I secretly
kicked Zhou Xuanyu.
Si is a brave kid.
Here.
I have two more pieces of candy.
Let's go.
Don't eat it yet.
Mom, eat the banana.
Honey,
you're a real heroine.
Turns out you're not only
tough at home,
but also bossy outside.
Word has spread all over the mine.
They say you scolded the principal
and scolded Zhou Xuanyu.
You were so logical when you got mad,
with good reasons.
I heard the principal was scolded by you
so much that he turned green
and didn't dare to say a word.
Dad, let me imitate Mom for you.
I know my own daughter.
I know what she's up to
just by looking at her.
Did I say that?
That sounds like something
your mom would say.
She doesn't cause trouble,
but she's definitely not afraid of it.
Mom,
after what you did,
I bet no one at school
will dare to bully my sister again.
Mom,
Zhou Xuanyu hits really hard.
My face still hurts.
So you know it hurts.
Let it hurt.
It'll teach you a lesson.
About you getting into a fight,
I haven't even settled the score with you.
Do you think what you did today
is something to be proud of?
How many times do you expect your dad
to fix these glasses for you?
Go.
Wash the mustard greens in the yard.
No dinner until you finish.
Mom,
my sister is the victim.
It's my fault for being late today.
Otherwise, that kid Zhou Xuanyu
wouldn't have been able to
lay a finger on my sister.
Don't go out.
I can handle it alone.
Brother.
You fought for me today,
and took the punishment for me.
I can't be disloyal.
Don't you think our mom is weird?
She fought everyone at school
to stand up for you,
but now she's punishing you.
What is she thinking?
That's just how our mom is.
She changes her tune
in the blink of an eye.
Those little brats
are such jerks.
Just scolding them today
was letting them off easy.
If you ask me,
they need a good beating.
Is this already too much for you to bear?
This is just the beginning.
They won't stop acting up.
Then, honey,
please enlighten me.
You.
Your daughter is just like you,
stubborn
and inflexible.
About what happened today,
even though it wasn't her fault,
she didn't handle it right either.
She still hasn't figured it out.
She's just different from others.
When people look at her,
they find her weird.
Right?
If someone says something to you today,
or touches you,
and you can't take it,
you get upset,
and then you want to
fight them,
will you ever
have a peaceful life?
Then what should we do?
She should learn
not to take other people's words
to heart.
Don't clash head-on with others.
Exactly.
Right?
Otherwise, she'll suffer in the future.
Honey,
you are so wise
and generous.
Come on.
Coward.
You're a coward who's afraid of bugs.
You're even afraid of bugs.
Cao Xin, get up.
Get up!
Qinglian.
Get up, get up, get up.
Leave.
What's wrong?
Si.
What's wrong with Si?
She...
Si seems to be...
That...
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
What's wrong with Cao Si?
I don't know.
Si.
Come.
Come with Auntie.
Alright, it's okay.
This is what happens when you grow up.
Don't be afraid.
Okay.
Come to Aunt Huo if you need anything.
Got it.
Alright, it's okay.
Thank you, Qinglian.
It's nothing.
Wait, wait.
Make a cup of brown sugar water for Si.
Use hot water. Here.
This...
Brown sugar water.
Do you want some?
Okay, thank you, Qinglian.
You're welcome.
Mom.
Qi Shi and I want
some brown sugar water too.
You're so nosy.
Hurry up, wash the vegetables
and hang them up to dry.
Qinglian,
Cao's family is about to
celebrate a happy occasion.
What happy event?
Cao
is finding love again.
What?
Look at that man.
Which man?
Don't make it so obvious.
That one.
He's Director Wang from Mine One.
The woman next to him
is his own sister.
She's the one
going on a blind date with Cao.
The matchmaker
is Director Zhang from our mine.
I heard
the woman is under thirty
and seems unable to have children.
So she got divorced.
That's why she's willing
to marry Cao
and become a stepmother.
Director Wang.
Don't worry.
Girl.
He's a wonderful man.
Really?
Really.
Director Zhang.
Thank you for this.
No problem.
Here.
I'm taking some time off to go home.
If the boss asks,
just say my child has an emergency.
Keep an eye on things for me.
You...
Where are you going?
This is so sudden.
Alright,
I'll make it up to you another day.
Qinglian,
what's wrong?
Did Qi Shi get into trouble again?
My mom is back.
Isn't Mom on duty today?
Quick, turn off the TV.
Cover it, cover it, cover it.
Hurry.
Write, write, write.
Aihua.
Something happened.
Isn't he insulting me?
Does he think I'm not dedicated enough?
He might be having a hard time,
but I'm still alive.
What does he mean?
What did you hear?
Let me hear what they're saying for a bit.
I can't hear clearly.
It sounds like only one of Mom
and someone else
can live.
What's impossible?
Today at our store,
Director Zhang brought people over.
Finding a stepmother for Cao Xin
is a slap in our face.
Cao Xin is getting a stepmother.
What?
I'm getting a stepmom.
People say,
when you get a stepmom, you get a stepdad.
You're about to get a stepdad.
Where's your sister?
She's dancing at school.
I'll go get her.
Don't go.
My sister is soft-hearted.
She might just agree to let my dad
find a stepmom.
It's going to rain,
and your dad is going to get married.
You can't stop it.
Haven't you always envied me
for having a mom who would mend your pants
and make buns for you?
Maybe your stepmom
will be gentle and handy,
and not loud like my mom.
I don't want a stepmom.
Song Qiang in our class
has a stepmom.
Then his stepmom
had a baby brother for him.
Once he got sick at school
and almost fainted.
His parents
didn't even come to pick him up.
Don't worry.
If you get sick
and your parents don't care,
I'll ask my parents to take care of you.
I don't want a stepmom!
Let's go.
I'll take you to find your dad.
Is that your stepmom?
Look at this house.
So new.
Really beautiful.
Here.
See that?
What do you want?
Are you tickling yourself?
My hand hurts so much.
Cry now. Don't waste this slap.
Cry now.
Hey, you three kids,
what are you doing there?
Isn't this Cao Dongfang's kid,
Cao Xin? Cao Xin,
why are you crying?
Cao Xin, why are you crying?
Did your dad hit you again?
This...
Let me see.
Cao Dongfang really hit you.
Cao Xin said his dad
loves to hit people.
He hits him whenever he's unhappy.
His mom got beaten a lot back then too.
Alright, Cao Xin.
Stop crying.
Cao Xin, stop crying.
Mom,
I want my mom.
Director Zhang.
Aren't you just messing around?
Director Wang.
Listen to me, Director Wang.
Let me ask him later.
Dongfang is not that kind of person.
Look at him.
What else is there to say?
Listen to me.
You...
There must be a misunderstanding.
What is there?
Let me ask him.
We'll talk after I figure things out.
Stop crying, Cao Xin.
It's okay now.
They're gone.
What's wrong?
Don't cry, Cao Xin.
Don't cry.
I want my mom.
Here.
Thank you, Aunt Huo.
-Thank you, Aunt Huo.
-You're welcome.
Here. You're welcome.
Every time Cao Xin and Si
come to our house for dinner,
we have delicious food.
The ribs Aunt Huo made are delicious.
Eat more if you like it.
If you want more later,
just tell Aunt Huo,
and I'll make it for you.
Just treat this place as your own home.
That's right.
What happened today
is between adults.
We adults have our ways to solve it,
you know?
Yes.
If you encounter this kind of thing again,
just tell me and Uncle Qi.
We'll stand up for you,
got it?
Don't try to
solve it yourselves.
How could you do that?
You guys,
aren't you risking
your own health?
Mom,
you're not mad?
I thought we ruined
Uncle Cao's date,
and would get a beating when we got back.
You are going to get a beating.
You just know how to make trouble.
Dad,
why do I feel like you're quite happy?
You've been grinning this whole time,
and haven't stopped.
Am I?
You saw right through me.
Dad.
Have you seen that woman?
My brother said she's pretty.
Is she pretty?
Very pretty.
And gentle.
Gentle?
But none of us like her.
Cao Xin and Si
don't want her to be their new mom either.
Cao Xin.
You don't like the new mom either?
I don't want a new mom.
She'll be mean to us.
Sister, you don't want
a new mom either, right?
We don't need a new mom.
We can often come
to Aunt Huo's house for dinner.
Aunt Huo is
just as good to us as our own mom.
That's enough.
Sister, you scared me to death.
I thought you wanted
a new mom.
How could I?
Aunt Huo is gentle and warm.
Uncle Qi tells jokes
to make us happy.
Your house is always lively.
We really like coming to Aunt Huo's house.
My mom is gentle?
Lively?
Isn't our family always chaotic?
Right.
You three talk too much.
Why do you have so much to say?
Hurry up and eat.
If you two miss your mom,
come to Aunt Huo's place
anytime.
Aunt Huo likes you too.
Director Zhang is really messing around.
How can a new mom
be better than your own mom?
Cao Xin, don't you like eating
sprout-stuffed buns?
They're heating up in the pot.
Take some back with you later.
Okay.
I'll go find Cao later
and have a chat.
Honey.
I thought about it.
I'd better go see him.
This way, I can explain it to Dongfang
clearly.
You are a woman,
it's harder for you to explain.
Dongfang.
Aihua.
I had someone buy
ten catties of mutton,
ten catties of pork,
and ten catties of eggs
from the cafeteria.
We can't finish it all,
so I'm giving half of them to you.
Keep it for yourselves.
We don't need it.
It's for the children.
Take them.
Okay.
Thank you.
Dongfang,
have a drink.
Okay.
Sit down.
Manyue has been gone for so many years.
I really didn't want to find someone else.
I was just thinking
about how to raise
these two kids.
Cao Xin is fine.
He's a tough boy,
so
it doesn't matter.
But Si,
being a girl...
If it weren't for Qinglian last time,
I wouldn't have known how to handle
that situation.
Then I thought,
if we could have
a woman in the house,
that would be good too.
Dongfang.
We all see your difficulties.
But look.
A stepmother
is just not the same.
And Cao Xin
would be the first to object.
If only his mother were still here.
Who says the Cao children have no mother?
I am his real mother.
I am.
Qinglian.
Come sit for a while.
There's a stool here.
Okay.
Dongfang.
Please don't mind.
I'll take care of Si's matters
from now on.
As long as I am alive,
I will treat Si
as my own daughter.
I'll vet her boyfriends for her.
I'll sew her quilt covers
when she gets married.
I won't let anyone say she has no mother.
How could I...
How could I mind?
I can't thank you enough.
Cheers.
Drink less.
You can't drink.
Dongfang, about your matter,
we will both keep it in mind.
If there's anyone suitable in the future,
I'll keep an eye out for you.
But the key is,
the kids have to like her.
Right?
Don't let it end up
like today.
Nothing is settled yet,
and it's already a mess.
Then it's better not to look for one.
Yes, that makes sense.
Makes sense.
Cheers.
Look in the mirror.
Among the children performing today,
Si
is definitely the prettiest.
Hurry up.
We still have to buy breakfast later.
There's no time to make it.
Wake those two boys up.
They'll be late.
Okay.
Aihua.
Here, breakfast.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Look how pretty Si is.
Si is the prettiest.
Are you happy, Si?
Si, just eat here.
Don't go back.
Okay,
that'll save time.
Get up quickly.
My God.
Is this a fairy descending to earth?
Two, da, da, three, da, da,
four, da, da, five, da, da,
six, da, da, seven, da, da,
eight, da, da.
One, da, da, two, da, da,
three, da, da, four, da, da,
five, da, da, six, da, da,
seven, da, da.
What are you looking at?
You want to dance too?
Forget it.
You're not suitable.
None of your business.
The midterm exam results
will be posted soon.
Let's see how you show off then.
Not bad.
Come on, let's practice in groups next.
Qi Shi.
Come on, let's dance together.
Si.
I don't know how.
I'll teach you.
Come on.
Follow my movements.
Stand like this.
Right.
Boring.
Cao Xin is always in first place.
Not necessarily this time.
First place is actually Qi Shi.
Cao Xin is second.
How is that possible?
Hello, Uncle Cao.
Qi Shi.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
Look.
What is this good stuff?
The bow hairpins I wanted the most!
That's right.
Come, put it on and let me see.
Let me hold it.
Does it look good?
It looks beautiful.
Qi Shi is Qingwu Town's
prettiest and
smartest little girl,
right?
How about this?
Next time
when you get first place again,
tell me
what you want.
Anything, even if it's expensive,
I will definitely buy it for you.
Okay?
Uncle Cao.
My parents said
I shouldn't just
take things from others.
They said it's impolite.
I'm not an outsider.
It's okay.
I know you are good to me, Uncle Cao.
Having the hairpins is enough.
I like them very much.
Thank you, Uncle Cao.
You're welcome.
You don't have to
take other people's things,
but when it comes to Uncle Cao's things,
you must take them.
Hear me?
Take them.
Alright, hold them well.
Okay, go home now.
Okay.
Look at you.
Mom and Dad work so hard
to pay for your schooling.
Look at your grades.
You failed two out of four subjects.
Do you want to
be like your dad
and go down the mine
to dig coal in the future?
Come, let me see.
Only the score for Ideology and Morality
is a bit higher.
You kid,
I don't know who you take after.
You just grew tall for nothing.
This score is not even as high
as my blood pressure.
Mom.
I had an exam too.
Give them to me.
Let me see.
How is it?
Look at your sister.
She got perfect scores in every subject.
We eat the same food in this family.
Where did your food go?
Did it go into a dog's belly?
That's my Sweetie.
She has a good brain.
She takes after me in this.
Dad.
I will study hard.
When I grow up, I'll support you,
so you won't have to go down the mine.
Come here, come here, come here.
Aren't you going to support me?
She'll support us all.
You really are my sweet little girl.
You know how to care for
Mom and Dad at such a young age.
You even know
it's hard for Dad to work in the mine.
Right?
How did Cao Xin do on the exam?
Him?
He's long been no match for me.
You're just showing off.
You're not modest at all.
Cao Xin used to
always get first place,
but he was never as arrogant as you.
Let's see what score you get next time.
Is this the essay you wrote?
Cao Xin.
Look.
What is this?
A camera.
Do you like it?
I promised you
that if you got first place,
I'd buy you a camera.
Even though you didn't
get first place this time,
I still bought it
because I promised you.
You're not mad
that I didn't get first place?
You win some, you lose some.
Not getting first place once in a while
is something
I can understand.
But I believe
that next time,
you will definitely get first place.
Right?
Good.
Here, take it.
Go do your homework.
Thanks, Dad.
Okay, go on.
Dongfang, Dongfang.
I was thinking,
since we
bought that new camera,
our family and Qinglian's family
could take a group photo together.
What do you think?
I think it's pretty good.
Then I'll tell Aihua.
Everyone is here.
Honey.
Alright, you look beautiful enough.
In all the surrounding villages,
there is no one
more beautiful than my wife.
What do you know?
This is our first time
taking a proper photo with our son.
This can be considered
our real family portrait.
Change your clothes
♪ An old sofa ♪
and look sharp.
My clothes are fine.
♪ A group photo
and several pots of flowers ♪
All right, let's go.
Go, go, go.
♪ A few words of everyday talk ♪
Grandpa, come join us.
Grandpa can't jump. You jump.
♪ I wish time could stop right now ♪
Three.
♪ The revolving winters and summers ♪
Four.
Mr. Cao.
Kids, come here.
Time for a photo.
♪ I grew up in the midst of chaos ♪
Coming, coming.
Come on.
Come, stand properly.
Come on, time for a photo.
♪ The world is full of changes ♪
Come on, hurry up.
♪ With the door closed,
I'm back to the old days ♪
Stand in the middle.
Then I'll stand in the middle,
next to Grandpa.
Okay.
To the middle.
Aihua.
♪ Countless times I searched for answers ♪
Aihua, to the middle.
Right.
Okay.
Come on.
♪ Can your life be better now ♪
Smile.
Let's all say cheese.
Ready.
♪ But I was born at the right time ♪
Three.
Two.
♪ When I open the door ♪
One.
Cheese!
♪ and get home ♪